thehealingcode.com 2011-04-17

# Privacy Policy

|  | 

|  Privacy Policy  
---  
  
Protecting our visitor's privacy is a priority for The Healing Codes  
(Dr. Alex Loyd Services, LLC).  
  
|  PLEASE NOTE: We are in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (S 877). The following policy represents our commitment to ensuring that your personal information is protected and your concerns regarding the management of your data are addressed and honored. Please send us an [email](mailto:privacy@adsational.com) if you have any questions regarding this policy.  
---  
This policy covers the following areas:  
Contact Information  
Dr. Alex Loyd Services, LLC  
2430 Vanderbilt Beach Road  
Suite 108-406  
Naples, FL 34109 

We can be reached via email at: [Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com](mailto:Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com)  
  
Information We Capture and Collect  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the customer's domain name, referring URL when possible, but not any personally identifying information.  
We collect only the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, aggregate information on what pages customers access or visit, and information volunteered by the customer, such as survey information and/or site purchases or registrations.  
The information we collect is for us to use to communicate with customers regarding our products and services, and to improve the content of our Web pages.  
With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that customers add to their shopping cart.  
Opt-Out Instructions |  Top  
If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by sending an email to [Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com](mailto:Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com), or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page. You may also use the opt-out instructions found at the bottom of every email communication from us to remove your address from our list. We will respect your request for privacy and will remove your address from future email communications. (Note: Please allow up to 10 business days for your request to be fully processed).  
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending an email to [Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com](mailto:Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com), or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page.  
Sharing of Information |  Top  
  
From time to time, we make our customer name, email and address information available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. Additionally, we may contact you via email about any orders-in-process or for the purposes of fulfilling an abandoned form from our site. If you do not want us to share your address information with other companies or organizations, please let us know by sending an email to [Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com](mailto:Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com), or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by sending an email to [Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com](mailto:Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com), or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page. Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.  
  
The CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (S 877) is a set of guidelines set forth by the government to help cut down on unwanted email solicitations. We applaud the government for taking action and will comply with the guidelines set forth as a legitimate commercial emailer. As such, we will make sure that anyone who opts-out from receiving our offers will be removed from our email list within a 10-day period. Also, we will work with 3rd party mailing partners to make sure that to the best of our knowledge, our opt-out list is also removed from their mailings when dealing with our offers. If you have given us your email address and have opted-out from our mailings, your address will be included in our "Suppression File" for this purpose. If you have any questions or concerns with this policy, please contact [Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com](mailto:Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com).   
Future Changes to Our Privacy Policy |  Top  
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically.  
Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending an email to [Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com](mailto:Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com), or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page.  
Correcting Your Contact Information |  Top  
Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in their contact information. Customers can have this information corrected by sending an email to [Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com](mailto:Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com), or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page.  
Security |  Top  
With respect to security, we use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving customer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.  
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Dr. Alex Loyd Services, LLC does not own or control, or to people that Dr. Alex Loyd Services, LLC does not employ or manage. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us by sending an email to [Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com](mailto:Privacy@TheHealingCodes.com), or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page.   

| 

| 

|   
---|---|---  

© 2007 Dr. Alex Loyd Services, LLC All Rights Reserved.
